Guide to the Florence Ledyard Cross Kitchelt Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Topical Files, 1920-1947; Series III
  - Staley, Eugene, 1938-42, undated (Box 24, Folder 293)
  - Stimson, H.R., 1936-41, undated (Box 24, Folder 294)
  - Stories and songs, poems for speakers, 1927-38, undated (Box 24, Folder 295)
  - Stout, Rex, 1941 (Box 24, Folder 296)
  - Sweeter, Arthur, 1936-44 (Box 24, Folder 297)
  - Taft, Horace D., 1929-43 (Box 24, Folder 298 - 300)
  - Thompson, Dorothy, 1937-41 (Box 24, Folder 301)
  - Toynbee, Arnold J., 1933 (Box 24, Folder 302)
  - Van Kirk, Walter W., 1937-38, undated (Box 24, Folder 303)
  - Veterans of Future Wars, 1936 (Box 24, Folder 304)
  - Wallace, Henry A., 1937-46, undated (Box 24, Folder 305)
  - Wambaugh, Sarah, 1935, 1939, 1943 (Box 24, Folder 306)
  - Washington, George, 1925-39 (Box 24, Folder 307)
  - Welles, Sumner, 1936-45 (Box 24, Folder 308)
  - Whelan, Frederick, 1925 (Box 24, Folder 309)
  - Whitney, Josepha, 1925-35 (Box 24, Folder 310)
  - Wilson, Woodrow, 1931-44, undated (Box 25, Folder 311)
  - Winant, John G., 1939-46 (Box 25, Folder 312)
  - Wolfers, Arnold, 1939, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 313)
  - World's Fair, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 314)
  - World Peace Foundation, 1928-39, undated (Box 25, Folder 315)
  - World Peaceways, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 316)
  - Wright, Quincy, and Louise, 1935, 1939, undated (Box 25, Folder 317)
  - Young, Owen D., 1933, undated (Box 25, Folder 318)
  - Youth movement, 1924-40, undated (Box 25, Folder 319 - 320)
  - Zeeland, Paul Van, 1938 (Box 25, Folder 321)
  - Oversize Poster, "General Pact for the Renunciation of War.", [1929] (Box DR121F0)